# AMIE FINCH

Knowledgea b 1 e p ha rm ac i st wi th two yea rs of expert e nee deliver! n g outsta n di ng se rvi ce i n a 67g Address Boulevard. community pharmacy. Comprehensive understanding of Medicare and Florida Medicaid billing and talent for providing sensitive and compassionate health care counseling to individuals. Excellent track record of delivering community health education programs and strong clinical and technical knowledge.

Miami. FL 76543 a. finch@myemail.com (765)432-1098

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **PHARMACIST**

Walgreens, Miami, FL July 2019 - Present

## **PHARMACY INTERN**

Memorial Healthcare Systems, Hollywood, FL January 2018-June 2018

- Advise customers about safe medication administration, including potential side effects and interactions with other drugs
- Accurately measure and dispense prescriptions and conduct medication reviews
- Create and deliver community education program on diabetes prevention and management
- Maintain patient confidentiality and handle sensitive and identifying information in accordance with data protection laws
- Supervise technician team and provide performance feedback, ensuring efficient and accurate medication dispensing
- Checked medication orders under the supervision of a precepting pharmacist to preempt potential drug interactions
- Prepared and d ispen sed prescri ptio n med i catio ns alo ngsid e experi enced pharmacy technicians
- Discussed individuals' care and medication requirements with their doctors
- Provided guidance for patience on healthy living and eating and referred to outside agencies where appropriate

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Biology University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL September 2011 - June 2015

Doctor of Pharmacy

University of Florida School Of Pharmacy, Jacksonville, FL, Septem be r 2015 - Ju ne 2019

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Kind and professional communication style
- Detailed knowledge of diabetes management
- Strong leadership
- Ex pe rience tra i n i n g a nd su pervi si ng technicians
- Able to m u Iti task and p riori t ize strategically

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Certified Diabetes Educator, 2020
- ♦ Nutrition Support Certification, 2021